For Hector, history has a way of repeating itself.
Being Human is a drama, comedy, fantasy film directed by Bill Forsyth.
One man must learn the meaning of courage across four lifetimes centuries apart.
Hector, played by Robin Williams.
The Storyteller, played by Theresa Russell.
Bambina, played by Maudie Johnson.
Bambino, played by Max Johnson.
Priest, played by Robert Carlyle.
Raider, played by Irvine Allen.
Being Human is a 1994 comedy-drama film written and directed by Bill Forsyth and starring Robin Williams, John Turturro,
Bill Nighy, Vincent D'Onofrio, Robert Carlyle, Theresa Russell and Ewan McGregor in his feature-film debut.
An international co-production of the United Kingdom and Japan, the film portrays the
experience of a single human soul, portrayed by Williams, through various incarnations.
Williams is the only common actor throughout the
stories that span man's history on Earth.
An attempt on director-screenwriter Bill Forsyth's part to depict by visual means the ordinariness of life
throughout the ages, Being Human is deliberately slow in its pace to emphasize how slow life often is.
The structure is one of vignette-like character studies of one man (actually five distinct men, all with the
same soul) who keeps making the same relationships and mistakes throughout his lifetimes.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.